LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now.
Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
Dona dona dona... Dona...
Taking the calf to market...
The cart sways...
Oh! Batou-San!
You guys... Do you understand
the meaning of that song?
Oh, please! Of course we do!
It's a song describing how a
calf gets sold to the market.
Yeah, in order preserve his existence,
man prioritizes economic factors over
sentiments, that's what it means!
Right, right! It's about friendship
being defeated by poverty!
Yeah, in the end.
Well... It seems that we're
being sent off to the lab.
All right then,
Bye-bye!
Chinks
in the
Armour
of the
Heart
Excuse me.
The arrangements for your departure have
been completed. This is in regards to
the request for infiltration and investigation by
the Prefecture Police's Public Safety division.
So, this is my new personal history, eh?
Make contact with Pavlo Zaitsov, who is
under surveillance for suspected espionage,
determine who abetted him in
espionage, and arrest them both.
Furthermore, eighteen minutes ago, there was a message
from the Chief, who is attending the international
Conference on Countering Global Terrorism, requesting that you
resolve the situation by the time he returns from Britain.
Hey, man.
Hmm?
Are you concerned that the
Tachikomas were sent to the lab?
Why would I be?
Well, it's fine if you're not.
I wouldn't want you to
worry yourself over me, now.
Well, I'm not "worried",
but you sure don't seem too enthused lately.
Oh? Not true.
I was a big fan of this Zaitsov dude.
Fan?
In any case, make sure you return this car
to Section 9 after I get into the base.
I know. I would never dream of
driving this antique around.
Keep it coming.
Come on.
Keep coming.
Put more power in your punches.
That's not it.
Have you been listening to me at all?
Sorry, but I didn't hear anything worth believing.
What...?
All right, if you doubt me that
much, give me your best shot.
So he says.
Give to him, it's what he wants.
All right, come get some.
Just kidding.
Oh, what's this? So, you're all talk?
A concussion? Lame ass.
What's wrong? Aren't you guys pissed
that one of you got taken down?
Try to get me.
Come on, who wants some?
Nobody wants to challenge me?
Cowards!
I'll take you on.
You're not new around here, are you?
All right then. I was thinking of
skipping a boring group training session,
but I heard that you've recently been assigned as a
fighting instructor, so I figured I'd actually show up.
Don't disappoint me, Mr. Silver Medal.
You have a good memory.
Yeah, How about it? Want to go with boxing?
You're good. You've studied
my style already, haven't you?
So, your fists still have some life left.
Oh...?
Hey, you all right?
What happened?
I took advantage of your implant's weaknesses.
I thought I'd be able to win.
I like you.
If you really want to know why you
lost, come to my house.
I'll explain everything.
I've been teaching my skills,
moving from base to base.
Those are all that I have left.
Hmm? You have a lot of these.
You've fought in this many tournaments,
and you've won practically all of them.
That's the only one that I didn't win.
I watched this match.
I was shocked... I didn't think you were
going to lose, not even for a second.
Heh, I was shocked, too.
Because of that one loss, everything went bad.
The media that idolized me and the
implant manufacturers all went away.
In that match... Why didn't you take
advantage of the implant's weaknesses?
Even now, I'm still not satisfied
with that match's outcome.
The implant's weaknesses, eh...
Yeah, "the implant's weaknesses."
That's what happened this afternoon, right?
That's why I'm here.
Oh, that?
To tell you the truth, there's a trick to it.
Looks like the conversation
is pretty lively this evening.
Oh, hi.
What's the topic?
Can I join in?
Hey, don't tell me you're serving that to a guest.
Don't we have more expensive liquor?
Oh? Price isn't everything.
In hospitality, it's the thought that counts.
You don't get it at all.
Hey, let's go out for drinks.
There's a place that serves really good liquor.
What's wrong? I don't mind this at all.
Don't say that. It'll be on me.
Sorry, that's an urgent call.
I'll be right back.
Sorry, he was in a good mood today for
once, so I thought we'd have some medovukha...
I think I made him upset.
"Medovukha"?
It's home-brew liquor that's made in our homeland.
I wonder if you'll like it.
Whoa, it tastes sweet!
Of course. It's made by fermenting honey.
You seem like a very good man.
Are you married?
Oh, yeah. I have one kid.
He's going to be six years old.
Really? You don't look the type.
Sorry, but something came up.
Let's go drinking some other time.
We can continue the discussion then.
Oh, okay. Too bad.
Please come by again.
Sure. I'll stop by soon.
Good night.
'Night.
Sorry about making you wait.
My guest went home.
All right, we'll send you
the next set of instructions.
Oh, morning.
Hey, is Batou around?
Batou? Oh, that guy from yesterday.
I haven't seen him around, no.
Oh, the man's well-known around here?
Oh, no. I think he's a member of the 103rd Air Force Division
that came in when the Mikumo made a port call yesterday.
What do you want with me?
Oh, so you are here.
How about lunch?
Lunch? I feel more like a shower right now.
I see. Well, guess I'll go on ahead.
Taking boxing gloves to lunch?
Don't disappoint me.
Yo.
How are you doing?
Here's the autograph... I thought this
would be better than signing a piece of paper.
Thanks! My nephew will be pleased.
That's good.
Oh, some good coffee beans came in.
Let me brew you a cup.
Don't trouble yourself. I have to go back soon.
I'll brew it quickly.
Would it be better if the
beans are coarsely ground?
Yeah, you have a metal mesh filter, right?
Okay, then yes, please.
All right, then...
Mmm, a Sagawa-made
decoy firewall, eh?
Using high-end stuff, aren't we?
By the way, there are some guys from somewhere who're
here for a group training session, aren't there?
Oh, are you referring to the Marines from
the aircraft carrier that made a port call?
Oh, maybe. Yesterday,
one of those guys came to the gym,
and he had some backbone.
Oh, really?
Yeah. He has some real potential.
That's nice. Do you think
you will become good friends?
I wonder... I'm not too good about making friends.
A double-layer firewall... Pretty damn cautious.
I wonder if the setup's to initially transfer
the data here and then to send it outside.
Where does he intend to redirect it?
What?
Is someone tapping my connection?
Damn it, I only have a little bit left.
Here you go!
Sorry, I just remembered
that I have an urgent errand.
Hey, now... Taking our sweet
time to transfer data, aren't we?
And you call yourself a spy? Slowpoke.
Now, where are you going to redirect the data?
Hey!
Did one of you enter my room?
No one's... inside, Sir.
Where are the "beans"?
They are ground.
Then, why aren't you starting the brew?
It seemed as though someone
was tapping my connection.
To be safe, do not use that brewer again.
It's highly possible that it's now tainted.
Yes. I'll make the brew elsewhere.
I'll put the current brew in a pot and wait.
I will tell you the delivery
location at a later time.
If you see an unfamiliar face
in your vicinity, be cautious.
An unfamiliar face...
Hey, Batou. Tonight the tab's
going to be on me for sure.
Come with me for a drink.
There won't be any sweet liquor.
A good place, don't you think?
Ever since I came to work here,
I haven't met any people worth my time, so I've
basically been hanging out here all the time.
I see.
It's the first time that you've ordered this.
Yeah, it seems like I've
finally found a friend, so...
That's good.
Oh yeah, you said you were married.
You must at least have a picture of your wife.
Show it to me.
I'm not that type of guy.
Oops, sorry.
That's expensive liquor, isn't it?
What a waste.
Sorry, can you go get something to wipe this up?
Sure.
"Not that type", eh?
You're hard to read.
I'll bring it to you right away.
Thanks.
He said he'll bring something later.
I see.
Another call...
Sorry, can you sit tight for a wh...
I don't mind.
Looks like you're as busy as one
of those intelligence people.
Where is the coffee pot?
I brought it.
Getting chilly, isn't it?
Hey, what is this?
What?
You just got a row of numbers!
Wait a minute, I just followed your
instructions to the letter and got data.
It's an error on your part that
the data wasn't what you wanted!
You disappoint me.
Don't blame me!
Pay me what you owe me!
Pathetic!
Batou!
You were followed!
You're... intelligence?
No, Internal Affairs?
You pretended you were a fan and approached me because
you were conducting an internal investigation?
I was deceived pretty well.
Did you study my past, too?
You wanted money?
Even though you said everything went wrong,
it seems like you had a pretty good life going.
What do you know about my life?
I want to ask you one thing before I arrest you.
It's that "implant's weaknesses" thing.
Heh, I see.
I guess I haven't told you yet, have I?
Come get me.
If you can beat me again by taking
advantage of these "weaknesses".
I'll let you go.
Are you joking? You'll never be able to beat
me, no matter how many times you try.
Then hurry up and come down here.
You'll regret that you put your gun away.
Enough with the chitchat, come get some!
Your implants can't beat mine in terms of output!
You... did you let yourself be
beaten on purpose yesterday?
Have you fallen so far that
you can't even tell if I did?
I see...
The one with a weakness in his heart... was me.
Oh, good evening.
I'm glad I ran into you.
Aren't you with my husband?
Oh, not anymore...
I was with him for a while, but...
I see, then we've run into each
other at just the right time.
Here, it might not suit your
tastes, but this is for your wife.
Oh, hey man... It's finished?
Yeah.
Er, what's wrong? You don't seem to be feeling any
better than before, even though the case was resolved.
Do I seem that way?
Aren't you?
H-hey!
Hey...
Dammit...!!!
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up